yourprivateproxy.com 2015-09-13

# Privacy Policy

Post date: 

Monday, October 21, 2013 - 04:22

Privacy Policy yourprivateproxy.com, ("yourprivateproxy") is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. This policy applies only to yourprivateproxy, and not to the web sites of other companies or organizations visited using yourprivateproxy's service. Our privacy policy statement will help you understand yourprivateproxy's commitment to safeguarding your private information. Information Collection and Use yourprivateproxy does not collect any personal or individually identifiable information without the informed consent of the member. We will not sell, share, or rent your confidential information to third parties, individuals or other organizations. Server Log Files We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for performance assessments and aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Our servers automatically record the following information about each request to our site. Intelligent Caching yourprivateproxy uses extensive caching technology to cache frequently requested Web content. Caching mechanisms are used to serve web pages directly from the yourprivateproxy local storage as a means to make web performance faster and more efficient. We do not cache or locally store any end-to-end web content transfers, like e-commerce transactions, via the Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Internet Cookies yourprivateproxy.com, may use a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer to maintain a session state. These short-lived cookies are not written to your hard drive and are removed when you close the browser. This means that not only are your web activities kept private, but also that your hard drive memory is not depleted. Our customizable user preferences feature uses a single cookie, which is stored on your local hard drive. This cookie is used for user customizable privacy options. yourprivateproxy does not, and will not, use cookies to retrieve personal information about you. Sharing We may share aggregate demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information and cannot identify any individual person. Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that yourprivateproxy is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information for their protection. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the yourprivateproxy web site. Newsletter If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Security This website takes every precaution to protect our users information. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. yourprivateproxy.com, is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have incorporated physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information. Notification of Changes A notice will be posted on this web page for 30 days whenever this privacy statement is changed.

Last modified

Tuesday, January 21, 2014 - 14:55

## Usage of private proxies

Before you **buy proxy** or **proxies** you should check the list of services that we don't allow. As a condition of your use of the **private proxies** we provide, you warrant that you will not utilize the **proxies** for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by our terms, conditions, and notices.

## Payment

We offer a **month to month service**. There is no contract or long term obligation. You are **billed on a monthly basis** , and if you cancel you will not be billed again. Currently, we only accept Paypal as a payment method but this is subject to change in the near future. 

Get you own private proxy plan with 1 montly ip replacement included!
